我曾是吸血鬼军队的一名精英战士I was an elite
soldier in the vampire army.
一个死亡行者A Death Dealer.
而且我还干的不错And I was good at it.
但我却背叛了But I was betrayed.
维克多,我们的长老和最强的吸血鬼...Viktor, our leader and the most powerful vampire...
我曾相信他是我们的救世主was not the savior he
had led me to believe.
突然之间,自己人变成了敌人Suddenly, allies turned enemies.
我曾效忠的吸血鬼的长老却希望我死The vampire Elders I had
once protected wanted me dead.
在我遇到麦可柯文后Then I found Michael Corvin.
不是吸血鬼也不是狼人,麦可变成了一个混血Neither vampire nor Lycan,
Michael became a hybrid.
我们进行反抗,并杀死了长老We retaliated, killed the Elders.
但是后来一切都变了But then everything changed.
我被抓住了,不知道的是我当时已经怀上了麦可的孩子I was captured, not knowing
that I was carrying Michael's child.
伊芙,我们的女儿,第一个纯血的混血...Eve, our daughter, the first pure-blood hybrid...
她的血液可以结束这场战争...whose blood could end the war...
高纯度的血液变成了吸血鬼和狼人都想要的became highly sought after by
both vampires and Lycans alike.
我唯一的选择是让她远离这世界和我自己...My only choice was to hide
her from the world and from myself...
这样他们就不会跟着我找到她so not even I
could lead them to her.
我曾是吸血鬼军队的一名精英战士I was an elite
soldier in the vampire army.
我唯一的选择是让她远离这世界和我自己...My only choice was to
hide her from the world...
这样他们就不会跟着我找到她so not even I
could lead them to her.
黑夜传说5
血战
我已经存活了很久甚至忘了时间I have lived beyond my time.
见识了上千个新月...Another new moon in
1000 years of new moons...
我已不在乎看到它了and I do not care to see it.
我什么都没有了I have nothing.
我的柯文...My coven...
我的女儿...my daughter...
-我的至爱,都不见了-拦住她!- my love, all gone.
- Cut her off!
也许,很快...And soon, perhaps...
我也将不存在my very existence.
-莎伦娜来了!-我正被追杀...
- Selene's coming!
- I am hunted...
被吸血鬼和狼人by vampires and Lycans.
现在我是一个无家可归的人,一个被排斥的人Now I am an outcast, a pariah.
-放倒她!-记住,他要抓活的
- Put her down!
- Remember, he wants her alive.
开枪!Fire!
现在开火,继续!Come on, now. Fire!
你可真是让人难以追踪啊You are an extremely difficult
person to keep track of.
我不需要你的帮助I don't need you.
但是谢谢你But thank you.
还在找关于麦可的消息?Any word with Michael?
-不要跟踪我!-我不是跟踪你
- Stop tracking me!
- I'm not tracking you.
我在找伊芙I'm looking for Eve.
好吧,我是最后能帮你找到我女儿的人Well,
I'm the very last person who could help you find my daughter.
莎伦娜,听我说.狼人又活跃起来了Selene, listen to me.
The Lycans are moving again.
不,这次不一样No, this is different.
他们是有组织的.他们有一个新的领导人They're organized.
They have a new leader.
-他叫马略斯.-我和这场战争无关了
- His name is Marius.
- I'm finished with this war.
好吧,你自己的事并没有结束Well, it's not finished with you.
他们会杀了你的...They could have killed you...
但显然他们的任务就是抓活的but clearly their mission was to capture you.
你女儿的血,它非常的珍贵Your daughter's blood, it's a prize.
如果他们找到她,如果使用它...And if they find
her, if they use it...
-马略斯的将会变得无比强大.-好吧,这样我更希望她仍然隐藏着
- Marius's power will be limitless.
- Well, then I hope she remains lost.
我需要你传递一个信息I need you to deliver a message.
理解了就坑一声Grunt if you understand.
告诉马略斯...Tell your Marius...
如果他以为从我这里可以得到消息...if he thinks he
can extract information from me...
来找到我的女儿,没用的to locate my daughter, he can't.
我不知道她在哪里,我也不想知道I don't know where she is,
and I don't want to know.
马略斯会找你的Marius will find you.
你知道你要怎么说了吗?Do you understand your message?
这是什么?What is it?
你以前见过这个吗?Have you seen this before?
没有...No...
但是我们需要把它弄出来but we need to get it out.
我们走Let's go.
B组一号,
OVER.车辆接近中Bravo one, over.
Car approaching.
-访问完成.-关闭大门
- Access cleared.
- Close the gates.
开始周边扫描Commencing perimeter sweep.
欢迎您回家,先生Privilege to welcome you home at last, sir.
萨米拉在她自己的房间里等您了Semira awaits you in her private chambers.
萨米拉?Semira?
卡西乌斯在哪?Where is Cassius?
当然,整个委员会都在等您的,先生...The entire council will
greet you, of course, sir...
但是萨米拉只是请求见一面but Semira requests just a few moments.
你叫什么名字?And your name is?
瓦尔加,先生Varga, sir.
我将试着记住你I shall try to remember it.
因为这个悲剧并采取相应行动...And act accordingly because of this tragic...
下去Leave us.
亲爱的汤玛士.已经...Darling Thomas.
It has been...
-多久没见了?-几十年- how long?
- Decades.
恭喜你了Congratulations.
恭喜你在议会已经有了一席之地I gather you have
a seat on the council.
这没什么可骄傲的I could not be more proud.
很遗憾,在这种日子不能庆祝你的归来It's a shame that your return
is not under more festive circumstances.
据说西方的议会已经被完全摧毁了It is said that the
Western Coven was utterly destroyed.
是的,确实是Yes, it was.
很庆幸你还活着It's a blessing you escaped with your life.
是啊,也有很多不幸的Well, many did not.
我们的种族已经死伤很多了There has been too
much death among our people.
这些都是布达佩斯议会的骨灰These urns are all that
remain of our Budapest Coven.
好吧,向你表示哀悼Well, you have my condolences.
汤玛士,我们快要输掉这场战争了We are losing the war,
Thomas.
如果我们继续这样,在五年内我们种族将会灭绝If we stay as we are, our
species will be extinct within five years.
这是卡西乌斯和你说的?Does Cassius share your view?
狼人在重整旗鼓,发展种族,决心消灭我们The Lycans have regrouped, replenished,
and are resolved to exterminate us.
哦,当然了,你这里很安全的.东方的议会是一个堡垒Oh, surely, you're safe here.
The Eastern Coven is a fortress.
我们已经不是你记忆中的议会了We are no longer the coven you remember.
我们比以前任何时候都缺少死亡行者We have fewer Death Dealers than ever before.
你这里好像都是新生的血族You seem to be surrounded by new cadets.
新生血族,没有经历战争而且并不多...Raw recruits, neither combat-ready nor numerous enough...
不足以击退狼人的大规模进攻to repel a large-scale Lycan attack.
从未有过大规模的狼人进攻吧There has never been a large-scale Lycan attack.
至少这样的从未有过At least not a coordinated one.
因为从未有过这样的马略斯There has never been a Marius.
这一点我承认很痛苦,有生以来第一次...Pains me to admit it, but
for the first time in my life...
我真担心我们的未来I genuinely fear for our future.
所以,你是怎么打算的?So, what is your plan?
萨米拉,你一直是个有计划的人Semira, you always have a plan.
你特意安排我们小会面的目的This little mise-en-scene you're performing has a purpose.
我不会读心术I am not a mind reader.
请对一个老者礼貌点...Kindly do an old vampire the courtesy...
告诉他为什么他被邀请到这里of telling him why he's been invited here.
莎伦娜Selene.
来吧,我们要继续前进Come on.
We need to keep moving.
有比这更近的安全的地方There are safe houses far closer than this.
我告诉你,被他们毁了I told you, they destroyed them.
现在情况不同了.来It's different now.
Come on.
但是你签署了对她进行追杀But you signed her death warrant.
当然了.我蔑视她Of course.
I despise her.
她杀了维克托.他以前都听我的She killed Viktor.
I was his regent.
直到他遇到了莎伦娜Until he met Selene.
那你是想让她去杀了马略斯?So you want her to hunt Marius?
我希望她能训练新生的吸血鬼...I want her to train our new recruits...
这样我们有百名死亡行者去杀马略斯so we have 100 Death Dealers hunting Marius.
我怀疑她会同意I doubt she will agree.
她唯一关心的是她的女儿Her only concern is for her daughter.
伊芙,纯混血Eve, the hybrid.
不幸的是,那个可怜的女孩有一半狼人血统Unfortunately, the poor girl is half Lycan.
吸血鬼的本来相对狼人的来说就弱...It's a vampire's instinct to condescend to Lycans...
而且狼人不担心进化but they're not afraid to evolve.
与此同时,我们有1500年不曾进化...Meanwhile, we stagnate from 1500 years...
这该死的"纯血统"真是荒谬of this damned "species purity" nonsense.
而且讽刺的是莎伦娜...And the irony is that Selene...
-她的血液比我们的都要纯净.-所以谣言是真的吗?- is probably the purest of us all.
- So the rumor's true?
她的血液融合了柯文纳斯的?Her blood has elements of the Corvinus strain?
她非常特殊She is special.
她让我的儿子起死回生了She brought my son back from the dead.
-她的血液让他的心脏重新跳动.-这不可能
- Her blood restarted his heart.
- Impossible.
我亲眼所见.我救了我儿子的命I witnessed it myself.
She saved my son's life.
维克托和艾梅莉亚Viktor and Amelia.
一起逝去的永恒Side by side for eternity.
如果我没记错的话,你非常喜欢艾梅莉亚You were very fond
of Amelia, if I remember.
-我需要你和我结盟.-她不会冒险来这里的...
- I need you to be my ally on this.
- She won't risk coming here...
除非整个委员议会邀请她unless she gets an
invitation from the whole council.
我根本不可能发出这样的提议And I could never solicit such a request.
卡西乌斯是保护旧传统的人Cassius is protective of the old ways.
他甚至不能容忍我在委员议会里He barely tolerates my seat
on the council as it is.
但现在是非常时期,汤玛士But these are desperate times,
Thomas.
这就是为什么必须要你去说服委员议会来邀请她And that is why you must
convince the council to invite her.
他们今晚到达They arrive tonight.
黎明警报.60秒后日出Dawn alert. 60 seconds to sunrise.
马略斯,各地首领都到了...Marius, the pack leaders have arrived...
我让他们在指挥室等你了and I told them to wait
for you in the war room.
我相信他们一定争吵的很激烈They're fighting like dogs, no doubt.
-我来处理.谢谢了.-好的
- I'll handle it. Thank you.
- All right.
-继续,继续.-对,对
- Go on, then.
- Right, right.
来这边,我这边Come around, come around.
不!听我的No!
Listen to me.
我们从中分开他们.这样做才是对的We're gonna wedge them in.
That's what we do.
从这一边到另一边,我们只要分开他们...From this side and that
side, we just wedge them in...
-然后里应外合.-从中分开?- and squeeze them out.
- Wedge them in?
这是你的计划?这一点用也不没有Is that your plan?
It's not going to lead to anything.
-他要生气了.-闭嘴!
- He's getting angry.
- Shut up!
停!Stop!
-你是个奴隶吗?-不
- Are you a slave?
- No.
那就不要像奴隶一样Then don't behave like one.
看这张地图Look at this map.
你们看到什么了?What do you see?
你们看到狼人争夺的区域了吗?Do you see Lycans fighting over scraps?
我告诉你们我看到了什么I'll tell you what I see.
沃利尼亚Volhynia.
诺德格.图林根州Nordgau.
Thuringia.
狼人的胜利The Lycan victories.
我看到了吸血鬼的死亡I see vampires dead.
我看到了整个地区歼灭I see entire regions annihilated.
但是我们继续自我斗争,我们就不会再有进一步的进展But we will get no
further if we fight amongst ourselves.
我们不能停歇...We must not rest...
直到我们摧毁了他们最后的据点until we have destroyed their final sanctuary.
团结,我们才会强大Together, we are strong.
当我们找到那个纯混血女孩时...And when we have the
blood of the hybrid girl...
我们将战无不胜we will be invincible.
格雷戈尔Gregor.
就剩你自己了You have returned alone.
-我们打的措手不及.-莎伦娜在哪?
- We were taken by surprise.
- Where is Selene?
-她放过了我.-为什么?
- She spared me.
- Why?
她想让我回来传个话To deliver a message.
她想让你知道她的女儿不知所踪了...She wants you to know
that her daughter is gone forever...
你永远也找不到...that you can never find her...
因为莎伦娜也不知道她躲藏在哪里because even Selene doesn't
know where she's been hidden.
你相信她说的吗?Do you believe her?
你能相信她吗?Do you believe her?
我放了跟踪器在她同伴身上I put a tracer in her companion.
很好...Well...
说明你不是完全无能的that means you're not completely incompetent.
忍着别乱动Try and stay still.
-这是什么?-某一种子弹
- What is it?
- It's some sort of bullet.
钻入你身体的速度比你自愈的快It's burrowing through you
faster than you can heal.
这是自动推进的It's self-propelled.
这就是我想和你说的.这些狼人不简单That's what I was trying to tell you.
These Lycans are sophisticated.
我不知道能不能及时取出它I don't know if I
can remove it in time.
好吧,至少你会尝试这让人感到安心点Well, the least you can
do is attempt to sound reassuring.
我要试着别害死你了I'm going to attempt not to kill you.
那是必须的That will have to do.
你需要我们给谁提供保护和特赦?To whom do you want us
to offer safe haven and amnesty?
-给死亡行者莎伦娜.-那个杀了维克托的莎伦娜?
- To Selene the Death Dealer.
- The same Selene who murdered Viktor?
我不需要提醒,卡西乌斯,她做了什么I need no reminder,
Cassius, of what she has done.
真为你感到丢脸Shame on you, sir.
我不想再听到她的名字了I will not hear her name spoken again.
卡西乌斯,我理解你的愤怒Cassius,
I share your outrage.
为何如此垫着?Whatever has possessed you?
如果我们不采取果断行动...If we don't act decisively...
两个星期内战争就在打到大门口the war will be at
your gate within a fortnight.
不过大门将依然存在And that is precisely where it will remain.
没有狼人敢攻击我们的议会No Lycan pack would
dare to attack our coven.
我们的防御系统会为他们开着Our defenses would rip them apart.
也许一些普通的狼人确实是...An ordinary Lycan pack, perhaps...
但是马略斯已经聚集了更加强大的力量...but Marius has gathered a
force far more powerful than any...
未经过证实的夸张而已Unsubstantiated hyperbole.
你需要莎伦娜You need Selene.
她的实力,她的领导,她和狼人的亲密了解Her prowess, her leadership,
her intimate knowledge of Lycans.
而且她的战斗技能是无人能比的And her combat skills are second to none.
他说的没错,她是我们最强的死亡行者He's right, she is the most
lethal Death Dealer we've ever had.
但是她杀了自己的族人But she killed one of her own.
不仅是最强大的而且是受人尊敬的长老...Not only the most powerful
and respected of the Elders...
保护着她,爱她就像爱自己的女儿一样her protector, who loved
her like his own daughter.
不能相信她She cannot be trusted.
她受到审判了She has been judged.
也许她也可以挽回Perhaps she can also be redeemed.
对我来说这样很痛苦,但是汤玛士是对的It pains me to say
it, but Thomas is right.
没人像她一样能在战斗中证明自己No warrior has proved herself more in battle.
她在我们对抗马略斯时是非常重要的...She would be invaluable
in our fight against Marius...
为确保我们能胜利她非常关键perhaps even the pivotal
element to secure our victory.
如果能找到她...If she can be found...
并来到这个议会...and sets foot within this precious coven...
我同意了,萨米拉,由你亲自承担责任...I will hold you,
Semira, personally responsible...
-控制好她.-当然- for controlling her.
- Of course.
入侵警报.入侵警报.入侵警报Intruder. Intruder.
Intruder.
入侵警报.入侵警报Intruder.
谁派你来的?Who sent you?
放下枪Drop it.
你们怎么找到这里的?How'd you find us?
外面只有少数的安全屋了There are only a
handful of safe houses left.
狼人要找也相当容易The Lycans made it rather easy.
东方议会的长老让我带你回去The council of the Eastern Coven
sent me to bring you in.
-为了审判?-不是
- For trial?
- No.
-为了您的安全,和大家的.-你不要指望我相信这事
- For your safety, and ours.
- You cannot expect me to believe that.
他们每个人都签了对我的死亡执行令Every single one of
them signed my death warrant.
-时代变了.-吸血鬼不会
- Times change.
- Vampires do not.
这是你父亲给你的This is from your father.
这信是真的吗?Is it authentic?
这是他的封印,他的笔记It's his seal, his handwriting.
委员会特赦了你并且给我们提供了安全的场所The council has offered you clemency
and granted us both safe haven.
-为什么?-马略斯
- Why?
- Marius.
这是委员会诚恳的要求...It is the council's humble request...
让你训练我们来击败他和他的军队that you train us to
defeat him and his army.
走.快Move.
Come on.
跟踪信号来自这边The signal's coming from this way.
听着,我知道你很不情愿...Look,
I understand you're reluctant...
但是作为委员会的客人,我们将受到古老规则的保护but as guests of the council,
we will be protected by law.
我父亲不会说谎,他和你并无纠葛My father wouldn't lie,
and he holds no grudge.
-和维克托更没有关系.-入侵警报.入侵警报
- He had no love for Viktor, either.
- Intruder. Intruder.
-是狼人.-入侵警报
- Lycans.
- Intruder.
-我们必须离开.-你应该接受委员会的提议
- We must leave.
- You should accept the council's offer.
-为了伊芙.-伊芙不需要我的帮助
- For Eve.
- Eve does not want my help.
我知道你想保护她.如果我们消灭了马略斯...I know you want to protect her.
And if we destroy Marius...
我们就清除了对她安全来说的最大威胁we destroy the greatest threat to her safety.
快走Now.
马略斯Marius.
我们刚才错过了他们We just missed them.
我不希望再听到"刚才"这个词I do not wish to
hear the word "just" again.
没有她就胜不了Either we have her or we have nothing.
你明白了吗?Do you understand?
-你明白了吗?-是的
- Do you understand?
- Yeah.
探戈C组接近中Tango Charlie approaching.
安全All clear.
周边安全Perimeter secure.
-欢迎光临.-欢迎我?
- Welcome.
- Am I?
委员会的资源和武器都将给你...Our coven's resources and weaponry are yours...
来把这些新生血族变成像你一样的死亡行者中精英to transform these raw recruits into
Death Dealers worthy of your name.
瓦尔加将是你的得力助手Varga will be your right-hand man.
他知道我们所有的优点和缺点He knows all our strengths and weaknesses.
他也是我们这杀死狼人最多的超过40个的杀手He is also our most prolific
Lycan killer with over 40 confirmed kills.
-这是我的荣耀.-大卫,欢迎你
- It's an honor.
- David, welcome.
-谢谢.-为了纪念客人们的安全到来...
- Thank you.
- To mark the safe arrival of our guests...
我已经安排了一个小晚会在冬季花园I've arranged a little
soiree in the Winter Garden.
真的没有必要.谢谢There's really no need.
Thank you.
胡说.大家需要纵情享乐一下Nonsense.
There's always a need to indulge in pleasure.
在这战争的年代...In times of war...
这个时刻对委员会来说是值得庆祝的this coven needs moments to celebrate.
汤玛士,大卫和莎伦娜的到来...The arrival of Thomas,
David and Selene...
是非常值得高兴的理由is reason aplenty to rejoice.
敬所有人To us all.
萨米拉,你为我们提供了安全的居所.谢谢你It's good of you to offer us sanctuary, Semira.
Thank you.
这是我的荣幸It will be entirely my pleasure.
告诉我,她的血液让你起死回生是真的?Tell me, is it true that
her blood brought you back to life?
是的,是真的Yes, it is.
我对她无以回报I owe her everything.
不过,如果你不介意,我父亲想和我说些什么But, if you'll excuse me,
my father requests my counsel.
汤玛士总是这样的无趣Thomas was always such a bore.
好了,萨米拉显然对你很感兴趣Well,
Semira's certainly taken an interest in you.
恩,这肯定不是相互的Well, the interest is certainly not mutual.
我们需要她的帮助We need her protection.
相反,我觉我才需要保护来远离她On the contrary,
I think I need protection from her.
异生物的战争The Battle of the Peste.
我们认为这个战争就是结束时...We thought it would be
the one to end the war...
是最后的战斗...the final conflict...
但是战斗仍然持续but here we are still.
我希望你看到我们对莎伦娜的仁慈是怎样的I hope you see my bid for
clemency for Selene for what it is.
是的,至少你能提供给她帮助...Well, clemency is the
least you can offer her...
把她女儿交易给狼人after bartering her daughter to the Lycans.
在这场战争中我失去了很多I lost so much during this war.
相信我,这所有的失败仍然困扰着我Believe me,
I am haunted still by all those I failed.
好吧,那你必须帮我保护她Well, then you must help me protect her.
她已失去的甚至超过我们的想象She has lost even
more than we can imagine.
且她对我来说很重要And she's important to me.
马略斯还在那...Marius is out there...
满嘴尖牙傲慢的,计划着我们的毁灭reeking of canine insolence, plotting our downfall.
我们不需要莎伦娜去杀他We do not need Selene to destroy him.
有我就可以I am more than capable.
不,瓦尔加,有你还并不足够No,
Varga, you are merely adequate.
幸运的是,我们不是被迫依赖你的能力生存It's fortunate that we're not forced to
rely on your skills for our survival.
我的小甜心...That, my sweet...
对付无趣的人...yet unimaginative bedfellow...
是我所擅长的is my area of expertise.
-我认为你应该...-瓦尔加,不要多想
- I think you should...
- Don't think, Varga.
你会伤到自己的You'll hurt yourself.
还有其他的方法来证明你的价值There are other ways to prove your devotion.
一块精致的碎片...Piece by delicate piece...
这个难题将水到渠成the puzzle will fall into place.
哦,耶...Oh, yeah...
耶...Yeah...
不要瞄准着狼人.要预测Don't aim where the Lycan is.
Anticipate.
切记...And remember...
狼人在狼的形态时是最脆弱的a Lycan is never more vulnerable
than when he's in wolf form.
-什么?-这没有道理啊
- What?
- That makes no sense.
在狼形态的时候,他们不能使用武器...In wolf form, they cannot use weapons...
且他们的想法会变得更加原始...and their thinking becomes much more primitive...
只会杀戮driven only by bloodlust.
-你杀了多少?-我从不在意这个
- How many have you killed?
- I don't keep track.
我的速度比狼人快20%I'm increasing Lycan speed by 20 percent.
请继续Please continue.
我们的人已经在探索了东方议会周边的弱点了...My pack has probed the
Eastern Coven's perimeter for weaknesses...
然而未发现and there are none.
有任何的直接攻击就会触发警戒...And any direct assault would trigger the lockdown...
使得议会牢不可破which makes the coven impregnable.
即使我们在损失了大部分力量打进去后...Even if we could break inside
without losing 90 percent of our force...
-他们也有战略撤退...-这- they have fallback positions...
- This.
-那也是...-能使用了吗?
- That can be...
- Is this ready?
是的Yeah.
当我们有混种血液的时候...When we have the hybrid's blood...
我们就发起对他们的进攻we launch against the Eastern.
找到莎伦娜,然后找到她的女儿Find Selene, and we find her daughter.
我自己的发明My own invention.
死亡行者必须学会的第一件事...One of the first things
a Death Dealer must learn...
是如何在一个狭小的空间里战斗is how to fight in a confined space.
当然,这个训练缺少的是不可预见的Of course, the one thing
this training session lacks is unpredictability.
也许你会赏脸给我和我的学生...Perhaps you'll indulge me and give my students...
我应该说你的学生.教导我们战斗的不可预见性I should say your students.
A lesson in combat's unpredictability.
这不仅是我们的荣耀,这还是宝贵的训练It would not only honor us, but
it would be invaluable to their training.
-我没...-请
- I don't...
- Please.
好了That's enough.
集合.我们去学习下...Gather round.
We are going to school you...
狼人的本性in the true nature of the Lycan warrior.
为了这节课中,我们尊敬的客人莎伦娜...For the sake of this
lesson, our esteemed guest Selene...
将是一名勇敢捍卫我们堡垒的死亡行者...will play the role of
Death Dealer bravely defending our fortress...
而我则是狼人恶棍...and I will take
the role of Lycan villain...
来摧毁这里的here to destroy it.
女士优先Ladies first.
佩服Impressive.
加油Come on.
今晚的学到的是:Tonight's lesson:
不要相信你的对手和所谓的荣誉Do not trust your
opponent to fight with honor.
他们是狼人.他们什么也没有They are Lycan.
They have none.
别动Don't move.
茄属植物(有毒)Nightshade.
毒素渗入到吸血鬼的血液里,通常是致命的Leeches into vampire cells, usually fatal.
但对于一个有她这样力量的,只有痛苦...But for one with her
strength, there will only be pain...
接着是肌肉麻痹followed by paralysis.
我要杀了你I'll kill you.
紫外线子弹UV bullets.
你真的以为我会原谅你杀死了维克托?Did you honestly think I
would forgive you for killing Viktor?
瓦尔加,你知道你要做什么Varga, you have orders.
瓦尔加!Varga!
你不需要你来训练死亡行者I don't need you to train Death Dealers.
我有瓦尔加就够了I have Varga for that.
我只需重整这个议会就可以了...All that I need to rule this coven...
结束这长远和狼人的战争只需要你的血液and end the march of
the Lycans is your blood.
尸体怎么办?What about the bodies?
发出警报Sound the alarm.
让委员会发现尸体Have the council find them.
莎伦娜犯下暴行的确凿证据Conclusive evidence of the atrocity committed by Selene.
有人突破了There's been a breach.
我们需要找到莎伦娜We need to find Selene.
-封锁现场了.萨米拉的命令.-站一边去
- Cordoned off.
Semira's orders.
- Step aside.
大卫David.
走吧Come.
有不止一种方法来穿行于这议会There's more than one way
to move around this coven.
艾梅莉亚在几世纪前留下了这些通道Amelia created these passageways centuries ago.
这通到哪里?Where does this lead?
通向私人的地方,包括萨米拉的To the private chambers, including Semira's.
他们到底对她做了什么?What the hell have they done to her?
Machinasanguinemexhauri(拉丁语:机抽干血)
放血Bloodletting.
萨米拉要莎伦娜身上最高宝的东西Semira wants Selene's most precious asset.
-这会杀了她的.-到最后,是的...
- This is going to kill her.
- Eventually, yes...
但这过程是十分缓慢的but it will be agonizingly slow.
看Look.
这是为了尽可能的打开并扩张动脉This is designed to open
the arteries as wide as possible.
如果我们稍有不慎,对她将是弊大于利If we're not very careful, we
will do her more harm than good.
小心Careful.
这是她的吗?Is this hers?
是的Yes.
莎伦娜只使用这种特殊的武器Selene uses only this particular weapon.
在城堡里一个我们都知道的叛徒A known traitor within our walls.
这正是我所担心的...This is precisely what I foresaw...
你向我保证你会阻止的and what you assured me you would prevent.
是你害死了他们Their blood is upon your hands.
-先生,我尽全力了...-不要跟我解释
- Sir, I did everything...
- Do not speak to me.
这真是不可宽恕There can be no mercy.
就算逃到天涯海角也要抓住她I want her hunted to
the ends of the Earth.
一定完成It shall be done.
而且我要抓活的And I want her captured alive.
知道了吗?Is that understood?
明白Perfectly.
-我们快没时间了.-好吧,带上她
- We're running out of time.
- All right, take her.
你必须向北走,远北地区You must go north, far north.
去瓦尔道尔Var Dohr.
别No.
背叛的父亲和儿子Father and son united in treason.
带上莎伦娜Carry on with Selene.
这里交给我了I'll deal with them.
加油Come on.
现在!快走!Go! Now!
不!No!
黎明警报.60秒后日出Dawn alert. 60 seconds to sunrise.
继续走啊.外面的太阳会把你化为灰烬...Go ahead.
The sun will burn you to ashes out there...
或者你可以在这里体面点死去or you can die
with some grace in here.
他们居然可以在阳光下行走They can walk in the sun.
你需要进食.你已经失血过多了You need to feed.
You've lost too much blood.
那个孩子...因为他帮助了你的孩子That child...
Because he helped that child of yours.
我的儿子已经死了.死了My son is dead. Dead.
大卫David.
带上她Take her now.
你必须向北走.去瓦尔道尔You must go north.
Var Dohr.
现在!快走!Go! Now!
谢谢你Thank you.
我很抱歉你失去了你的父亲I'm very sorry that you lost your father.
他英勇的战斗到了最后He put up a valiant fight.
奇怪的是感觉失去一个你好像从未真正了解的人It's strange to lose someone you
feel like you never really knew.
我对我母亲有同样的感觉,但是...I feel the same about my mother, but...
我几乎没有她的记忆I have almost no memory of her.
我和伊芙And I of Eve.
我不想她I didn't want her.
我不了解她I didn't know her.
我现在也失去她了And now I've lost her.
你为什么坚持说你已经失去她了?Why do you insist on
saying that you've lost her?
她让我承诺我永远不要去找她...She made me promise I
would never look for her...
就当自己没有个女儿that I would never
consider myself having a daughter.
她是对的And she was right.
这样对我爱的人没有好处Nothing good has come to anyone I love.
你的家人,和你就是我剩下的全部You're family, and you're all I have left.
那么,还真的是麻烦你了Well, then, you really are in trouble.
你需要休息You need to rest.
莎伦娜很显然是在与狼人结盟Selene's clearly in league with the Lycans.
背叛的汤玛士和大卫也是同谋Thomas and David were complicit in this treachery.
他们能在阳光下行走.这就足够证明他们勾结狼人了They walked in the sun.
This alone is evidence of Lycan collusion.
莎伦娜必须从我们的历史中抹去Selene must be wiped from
the pages of our proud history.
亚历克西娅Alexia.
-我们要报仇了.-拭目以待
- We shall avenge our fallen.
- See to it that you do.
-你用了多少毒药?-我认为最好宁可...
- How much nightshade did you use?
- I thought it best to err on the side...
瓦尔加,我说话的时候你在想什么?Varga, what have we said about you thinking?
毒药会消融的The poison will dissipate.
我需要的是纯净的的血,我现在就需要I need this blood untainted,
and I need it now.
这个不能操之过急It cannot be rushed.
这必须顺其自然It must run its course.
绝对是这辆车It's definitely the car.
但是没有他们的踪迹But no sign of where they went.
扩大范围到整个城市Spread out across the city.
搜索所有地方Search everywhere.
本列车将停留在四号站台The train at platform
four terminates at this station.
去北方Northbound.
我将会更加的强大...I will be more powerful...
比卡西乌斯还强...than Cassius...
比这个议会的任何一个都强大than any vampire in this coven.
-搜寻的如何了?-莎伦娜和大卫他们向北方去了
- What news of the search?
- Selene and David are heading north.
-他们当然向北了.-夫人?
- Of course they are.
- Your Grace?
他们会跑到仅存的议会...They will run to the only remaining coven...
庇护他们的议会:瓦尔道尔,北欧堡垒to afford them safe haven:
Var Dohr, the Nordic fortress.
但是瓦尔道尔只是个传说But Var Dohr is only a legend.
我不会给它如此高的评价I would not give
it such an elevated status.
那是一个寒冷的,沉闷的前哨,都是可怜的和爱好和平的懦夫It is a frigid, dreary
outpost full of pathetic, peace-loving cowards.
你说的好像你已经去过那里You speak of it as
if you have actually been there.
当维克托陪着莎伦娜浪费时间的时候你认为我在哪里?Where do you think I was
when Viktor wasted years with Selene?
自己做好准备Prepare yourself.
路途遥远,我需要你单独完成任务The journey's long, and I
need you to take it alone.
我必须确认叛徒在那...I must be certain the traitor's there...
在我冒着风险从议会派出一整队的死亡行者之前before I risk sending a full squad
of Death Dealers so far from this coven.
你要更小心点You need to be more careful.
你要再温柔点You need to be more gentle.
-你找到莎伦娜了?-是的
- Have you found Selene?
- Yes.
她确实前往北欧的议会了She is headed for the Nordic Coven.
为此我将不惜一切I risk everything for this.
-为了你,为了我们.-亲爱的,我知道
- For you, for us.
- I know, my love.
为了力量萨米拉越来越疯狂了Semira grows more insane
for power with each day.
必须阻止她She must be stopped.
每一天,我越加害怕如果我们被发现她会怎么办And every day,
I fear more what she will do if we are discovered.
没有纯混血我不能进攻东方议会I cannot attack the Eastern Coven
without the blood of the hybrid.
它太强大了,即使对我种族来说It's too strong, even for my horde.
莎伦娜...Selene...
她是狼人和吸血鬼一样关键的未来She is the key to the
futures of Lycans and vampires alike.
你必须拥有她You shall have her.
瓦尔道尔就在山的那一边Var Dohr is just beyond that ridge.
人都去哪里了?Where is everyone?
小心点Watching.
我们寻求庇护...We come seeking sanctuary...
不是来争斗的not to fight.
那么你来对地方了Then you've come to the right place.
我叫莉娜My name is Lena.
跟我来Follow me.
刚才发生什么了?What was that?
某种小把戏吧Some kind of trick.
你一定莎伦娜吧You must be Selene.
伟大的死亡行者真是来寻求和平的吗?Does the great Death
Dealer truly come in peace?
-是的.-那这另一位呢?
- I do.
- And what about this one?
这位是大卫,汤玛士儿子This is David, son of Thomas.
一个我很多,很多年未见的人了Who I haven't seen for many, many years.
请原谅我的失礼You must excuse the attention.
设计之初,我们的议会不能接待这么多的客人Our coven doesn't receive many guests, by design.
我们随心所欲...We do as we wish...
-而不是像别人那样生活.-那狼人呢?- not as others would have us do.
- And what of the Lycans?
离的太遥远了他们没有注意到...We are too far removed
for them to take notice...
即使他们注意到了,这里的气候环境对温血的狼人来说是巨大的障碍and even if they did, our
climate is quite an obstacle to warm-bloods.
如果没有你母亲的恩准...This coven wouldn't exist...
-就没有这个议会了.-你认识我母亲?- without your mother's grace.
- You knew my mother?
所有吸血鬼都认识她,我的孩子All vampires do, my boy.
不对.我的母亲出身卑微.她在分娩我后死亡了No.
My mother was low-born.
She died giving birth to me.
那是谎言,你会发现,旨在保证真正的血统的安全A falsehood, you will find, designed
to keep your true lineage safe.
-那她还活着?-不
- Is she still alive?
- No.
她的死亡对我们来说是个可怕的打击And her death was a
terrible blow to our kind.
我们举行了整整持续一个月的哀悼仪式The mourning ceremony we held
lasted for an entire month.
这通常是留给一个尊贵血统的荣誉...Such an honor is
usually reserved for a high-born...
-一个伟大的长老.-是的- a Grand Elder.
- Yes.
-艾梅莉亚.-是的
- Amelia.
- Yes.
我的母亲怎么会是大长老...How could a Grand
Elder have been my mother...
而且我从未听说?and I not been told?
我有东西给你I have something for you.
你的父亲最伟大的作品,纯银打造Your father's greatest work, infused with silver.
狼人们见到了都会胆怯The Lycans will cower from
the very sight of it.
-它真漂亮.-汤玛士知道有一天...
- It's beautiful.
- Thomas knew that one day...
你会被敌我双方的所围堵...you would be beset
by enemies on both sides...
他是对的and he was right.
大卫,这意味着你才是合法的东方议会继承人David, this means that you are
the rightful heir of the Eastern Coven.
你的父亲和母亲花了好几个月...Your mother and father spent many months...
加强了这里的安全within the safety of these walls.
维克托起了怀疑Viktor grew suspicious.
然后你的父亲就把你...Then your father spirited you away...
在萨米拉和她的军队赶来之前带走了before Semira arrived with her troops.
-那我的母亲呢?-她回到了东方议会
- And what of my mother?
- She returned to the Eastern Coven.
她当时的眼神...The light in her eyes...
不要说的好像她特意做出了牺牲一样Don't try and fabricate some
kind of martyrdom for her.
我更喜欢这样诚实地评价她的决定I prefer a more
honest appraisal of her decision.
她为了委员会,放弃了她唯一的儿子She abandoned her only son for
the sake of her precious council.
-拿回去.-大卫
- Take it.
- David.
大卫David.
艾梅莉亚让我把这个给他Amelia asked me to give him this.
你需要什么吗?What do you need?
不需要.只想自己静一静Nothing.
I just need to be left alone.
是的,这种感觉我知道Yes,
I know the feeling.
为什么我父亲不告诉我有关母亲的事?Why didn't my father
tell me about my mother?
我不是很了解你的父亲...I did not know your father well...
但我知道,他很害怕失去你but I know that his
greatest fear was to lose you.
似乎每一个家长都会让孩子失望It seems it's the curse of
every parent to disappoint their child.
-至少你为了你的孩子在战斗.-是的,但也失去了
- At least you fought for your child, Selene.
- Yes, and lost.
你有血统继承权的,大卫.你的母亲是位长老You have pure-blood heritage, David.
Your mother was an Elder.
你的父母护你安全是有原因的Your parents kept you safe for a reason.
他们保护你,希望有一天你能够领导家庭They protected you so that
one day you could lead.
这是你母亲留给你的礼物Your mother left you a gift.
哦,你真是太好了,但我不需要饰品Oh, that's very kind of you,
but I have no use for jewelry.
这戒指不单单是礼物The ring is not the gift.
它包含的是:一个母亲的爱It contains the gift: A mother's love.
有一滴她的血液A single drop of her blood.
也许它可以帮助你做决定Maybe it'll help you decide.
你来的正好You're just in time.
-来.-这些是什么?
- Come.
- What is this?
-中间的是艾丽萨.-她死了吗?
- Valissa, the in-between place.
- Is she dead?
没有No.
她是...She is...
一种生华becoming.
她服下了毒药She took a poison.
带着她去往神圣的地方It allows her to visit the Sacred World.
当她归来时,她会用新的眼光看待这个世界When she returns, she will
see this world with new eyes.
这么做我不明白I don't understand what this is.
我们早就知道有不只是这个世界We have long known there
is more than just this world.
当我父亲第一次带我下来...When my father first brought me down here...
就和你现在的感觉一样...I felt as you do now...
我是我已经往返神圣的世界很多次了but I have since been
to the Sacred World many times.
我的眼睛看到了很多超越表面的事情My eyes see beyond the
surface of so many things.
-我看到很多关于你的.-比如?
- I see much about you.
- Such as?
我看到了你和狼人相爱...I can see you've loved a Lycan...
-杀死了一个吸血鬼长老,怀孕新生...-停- killed a vampire Elder, and given birth...
- Stop.
我看到你已经失去了你的女儿...I see you have lost your daughter...
这让你的内心深处非常的痛苦...and how much pain
this gives you deep inside...
并且你一直隐藏着它where you will always hide it.
她是个特别的孩子She's a special child.
会经历很多的战争...Many battles will be fought...
最终失去她and lost over her.
-你还看到什么了?-黑暗
- What else do you see?
- Darkness.
关于我们所有人的One that touches us all.
如果你想保证她的安全,你需要更进一步...If you want to keep her
safe, you will need to go further...
甚至要比你现在达成的名声更进一步than even a warrior of
your renown has ever ventured before.
我见识了这么多的战争...I have seen so much war...
和这么多的杀戮so much killing.
我已经无法忍受I cannot bear more.
你在这里感受到的和平是真实的The peace you will feel here is real.
它渗入肌肤,安抚你的灵魂It seeps into your
skin and comforts your soul.
告诉我关于这个神圣的地方Tell me about the Sacred World.
水即是路The water is the path.
艾梅莉亚!Amelia!
我的儿子民大卫I name our son David.
大卫David.
有一天,你会明白的One day, you will understand.
我非常的抱歉I'm so sorry.
有狼人!发出警报!Lycans!
Sound the alarm!
关上门!Close the doors!
快!Move!
就如我说的和平,战争已经跟随着你Just as I spoke of
peace, war has followed you here.
保护好自己Protect your own.
我必须找到大卫I must find David.
-我们不得不让你离开.-不.是我们把狼人引到这来的
- We have to get you away.
- No. We led the Lycans here.
我们不能让这些人因此而死We can't let these people die.
快跑!Run!
这边,伙计们This way, men.
绕过去Go around that side.
她在这There she is.
你这害虫You parasite.
快杀了我Just do it.
马略斯Marius.
终于At last.
在你右边!On your right!
我对你期望更多I expected more from you.
告诉我你的女儿在哪里Tell me where your daughter is.
我不知道I don't know.
莎伦娜,我想要的只是她的血Selene, all I want is her blood.
只有她才能结束这场战争Only she can end this war.
我向你保证她不会有生命危险I give you my word
she will not be killed.
你到底是什么?What are you?
告诉他你女儿在哪里...Tell him where she is...
这样才能结束这无尽的杀戮and all this butchery will be over forever.
我真不知道I don't know.
你撒谎Lies.
他们走了They've gone.
麦可Michael.
-我放了你们.-看这眼睛
- I freed you.
- Look at the eyes.
我是谁?你知道我是谁吗?Who I am?
Do you not know who I am?
-我的女儿.-我不需要你
- My daughter.
- I don't want you.
不要来找我Don't look for me.
她说的是实话She's telling the truth.
她也不知道She doesn't know.
我的时间结束了My time is done.
他们在撤退They are retreating.
我的时间不多了I'm running out of time.
现在我们必须进攻东方议会We must strike against the Eastern Coven now.
你知道你必须要做什么You know what you must do.
水即是路Water is the path.
莎伦娜Selene.
赞美天...Praise the day...
在结束时when it ends.
赞美冰...Praise the ice...
在冰封时when it holds.
赞美剑...Praise the sword...
在杀戮时when it kills.
赞美生命...Praise the life...
蕴育永生that has lived.
是时候了It's time.
力量Power.
如此诱惑而简单的东西Such a seductively simple thing.
拥有你就拥有了一切Either you have it
all or you have nothing.
多么的迷人How fascinating.
艾梅莉亚...Amelia...
水即是路The water is the path.
大卫,你应该留在这儿You should stay here, David.
这里将是你的家This can be your home.
马略斯正在向东Marius is heading east.
现在没有什么能阻止他There's nothing stopping him now.
我的子民还在他的围攻之下And my people are beset
with enemies on all sides.
我怎么能在这生活...How can I stay here and live...
-让他们死吗?-他们需要一个领袖- while they die?
- They need a leader.
门口安全.检查周边Gate secure.
Perimeter check.
想我吗?Miss me?
-东边安全.-检查西边
- East gate is clear.
- West gate clear.
开始周边扫描Commencing perimeter sweep.
安防系统
确认关闭
授权完成Access granted.
带了什么消息回来?What news do you bring?
一场屠杀A massacre.
狼人攻击了瓦尔道尔堡垒The Lycans attacked the fortress of Var Dohr.
狼人在北方Lycans in the north.
北欧议会被打的措手不及The Nordic Coven was taken completely by surprise.
-大量的吸血鬼被杀.-莎伦娜也死了吗?
- Dozens of vampires have been killed.
- Was Selene amongst them?
死了.被马略斯亲手杀死Dead.
Killed by Marius himself.
真是莎伦娜去了哪,麻烦就跟到哪啊Wherever Selene goes, trouble surely follows.
-大卫呢?-我不知道
- What of David?
- I do not know.
我只想早点赶回来.也许可以帮上什么忙I only wished I had arrived sooner.
I might have helped in some way.
恩,你确实帮上很多忙了Well, you've helped in so many ways.
足够了,你所做的就像我希望和计划的You've done exactly as I
hoped and planned, if not more.
你看,信息就是力量You see, information is power.
我热情地收集它们And I collect it with a passion.
谢谢你带着马略斯去了北欧议会Thank you for leading
Marius to the Nordic Coven.
你的狼人爱人...Your Lycan lover...
对他一时的成功一定感到高兴must be delighted with his momentary success.
你以为我不知道You thought I didn't know.
愚蠢的女孩Foolish girl.
黎明警报.60秒后日出Dawn alert. 60 seconds to sunrise.
狼人灾难性的摧毁了整个委员会The Lycan scourge destroyed an entire coven.
躲在这些墙后面增加了他们的优势To hide behind these walls increases their advantage.
我们不能和马略斯开战We cannot take the war to Marius.
那我们就应该躲在这些安全墙里...Should we cower in
the safety of these walls...
-好让他逐个的干掉我们?-注意你阴险的言语,萨米拉- while he picks us off one by one?
- Curb your insidious comments,
Semira.
这个议会已经存在15个世纪了This coven has held for 15 centuries.
-它将继续存在.-我希望你能展示实力...
- It will hold for 15 more.
- I hoped you would show strength...
虽然我也愿意和有能力胜任though I was willing to settle for competence.
但是我错了I was wrong.
你这是什么意思What is the meaning of this?
如果这个委员会太弱不能采取行动...If this council is
too weak to take action...
那就让我来吧it is my duty to do so.
你被解除了你作为议会长老的职责并立即生效You are relieved of your
duties as council members effective immediately.
归来的叛徒The traitor returns.
哦,你是一个在这时候出现的傻瓜Oh, you are a fool
to show your face here.
我会让你为你所做的一切付出代价的,萨米拉I will make you pay for what you've done,
Semira.
我们在这交谈的时候马略斯和他的军队正向这边而来Marius and his army are
heading this way as we speak.
-我来拯救我的子民.-你的子民?
- I come to save my people.
- Your people?
杀了他.杀了他Kill him.
Kill him.
你为了成为你种族的守护者不惜一切代价...You aspire to be
the protector of your bloodline...
然而,你为了追求权力杀了自己的族人yet you kill your own
kind in pursuit of power.
现在结束了It ends now.
我是大卫,大长老艾梅莉亚的儿子I am David, son
of the great Elder Amelia.
我是这个议会的合法继承人And I am the
rightful heir to this coven.
艾梅莉亚没有儿子Amelia had no son.
嗯,她有远见...Well, she had the foresight...
知道我说的会受到质疑to know that my claim would be challenged.
给委员会的For the council.
艾梅莉亚Amelia.
他说的是真的His claim is true.
大卫是最后的纯净血统David is the last of the purebloods.
无所谓的.你们寡不敌众Irrelevant.
You are outnumbered and outgunned.
瓦尔加,你的命令仍然存在.杀了他Varga, your orders still remain.
Kill him.
-我说,"杀了他."-不
- I said, "Kill him."
- No.
你发誓为我效忠You swore to serve me.
我发誓要保护这屋子里的领导人I swore to protect
the leader of this house.
异常检测Breach detected.
-安全系统激活-是狼人.他们来了
- Security system engaged.
- Lycans. They're here.
在议会审判她前锁好她Lock her away until she
can be judged by the council.
安全系统激活.异常检测.安全系统...Security system engaged.
Breach detected.
Security system...
-她想的战斗来了.-瓦尔加,我仍然可以原谅你
- She gets her damn war after all.
- Varga, you can still be forgiven.
堵住她的嘴Gag her as well.
快,把卡车开过来.抬走Come on, move that truck.
Move it.
注意你的枪口!Watch your angles!
出发!Let's go!
坚守你的位置Hold your positions.
-在楼梯上!-在你后面!
- On the staircase!
- Behind you!
-撤退!-撤退!
- Fall back!
- Retreat!
到栏杆后面!Behind the balustrades!
干掉他们!Take them out!
-快走!-走,走,走!
- Come on!
- Move, move, move!
抬过来!Move it!
该死的Fuck.
准备瞄准!Aim at the ready!
开火!Fire!
躲开阳光!Hide from the light!
跑!Run!
走!Move!
射击,射击!Shoot, shoot, shoot!
这不可能Impossible.
我看到你死了I saw you dead.
我来了I'm here.
我起死回生了I brought backup.
他们太多了There are too many of them.
我已经把你杀了的I've already killed you.
马略斯!Marius!
-马略斯.-别
- Marius.
- Please.
我希望你父亲能活着看到I wish your father
was alive to see this.
他可笑的以为你能统治这个议会...His ridiculous dream of you ruling this coven...
这是如何害死你的will be the very thing that kills you.
没打中Missed.
哦,果然有效Oh, it worked.
我们是同类I'm one of you.
不!别!不!No! No! No!
你杀了麦可You killed Michael.
这是他最后留下的东西This is the last of him.
你的家人,和你就是我剩下的全部You're family, and you're all I have left.
你知道我是谁吗?Do you not know who I am?
你们的首领已经死了Your leader is dead.
带着你们的人.离开Take your wounded. Leave.
滚!Leave!
我们在最黑暗的时刻进行了最伟大的战斗We fought our greatest
battle in our darkest hour.
吸血鬼和狼人经过几个世纪的战争...After centuries of war between vampire and Lycan...
这可能是一个和平时代了this may at last
be a time of peace.
我们必须再次照顾我们的伤员...We must once again tend to our wounded...
和纪念逝者honor our fallen.
我们最后的两个组织必须寻找力量和团结...Our final two covens
must find strength and unity...
治愈并从灰烬中重生to heal and rise from the ashes.
我的旅程现在也算圆满了My journey has now come full circle.
曾经被遗弃的人,现在我是三大长老之一Once an outcast,
I am now one of three chosen Elders.
从被追杀到最高荣誉From hunted to the highest honor.
我已经活了1000年I have lived 1000 years.
我可能再多活个1000年...I may live 1000 more...
或者我明天会死去or I may die tomorrow.
但我不再惧怕死亡...But I no longer fear death...
因为我已死过一次了for I have known it once already.
我重生了...I am reborn...
我用双眼看到了神圣的世界...and my eyes have been
opened to the Sacred World...
和对未来的窥视and to the promise of
what is yet to be.
这不是开始There is no beginning.
也不是结束There is no end.
而是只是过程There is only becoming.